## web developer

# huyhuynh

### huyhuynh85@gmail.com 408.910.1012

#### **PROFILE**

My passion for creating and tinkering led me to switch to a career where I can make meaningful things that enrich the lives of others while also giving back to the community. I bring with me teamwork, analytical and communication skills carefully developed over the past six years from the marketing, marketing research and publishing industries.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Recent Graduate

2015

Dev Bootcamp

- Completed a 19-week immersive web development program
- Focused on Object Oriented Programing, Rails and JavaScript
- Emphasized Git, continuous integration and testing
- Provided constant feedback and employed empathetic approaches to other students and staff

#### Motorcycle Rider Coach

2012-now

Northern Illinois University

- Lead groups of students and teach them the fundamentals of motorcycle operation and safety
- Manage and reduce risk to maintain a safe learning environment

#### Accountant/Payroll

2014-2015

rEvolution Marketing

- Worked with multiple departments to migrate all current and historical accounting/HR data to new systems
- Ensured vendors/payroll checks were paid properly and on time

#### Accountant/Project Manager

2010-2014

Fieldwork Chicago O'Hare

- Provided a high quality of service through managing research projects and recruiters
- Hired and trained over half of client service staff
- Managed all cashflow including keeping up with collections and cutting costs

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California at Santa Barbara

2004-2008

- Bachelor of Arts in Business Economics with Accounting Emphasis
- Studied Globalization at Fudan University in Shanghai, China, Fall 2007

#### **SKILLS**

Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, Git, API, JavaScript, AJAX, jQuery, CSS, Sass, HTML5, Bootstrap, ActiveRecord, PostgreSQL, SQLite, RSpec, Capybara, Jasmine, Teamwork, Customer Service, Time Management

#### **PROJECTS**

Friendlier

May 2015

Rails

A dating site for friends to vet your potential dates before you meet them. Features image uploads and user messaging.

#### ShinetheChi June 2015

Rails

Mobile first app to view and report 311 service requests through Chicago's API. Features Bootstap grid and Google Maps.

#### Little Victories May 2015

Sinatra

Users can save and read small successes made throughout the year. Features AJAX and taggings.

#### DBoards May 2015

Sinatra

A CRUD app that allows anyone to upload and tag images of whiteboards. Features tagging and uploads.